Good, my man.
All right, media room. Can we just
unmute real quick and get started?
Okay, go ahead, guys.
Hey, congratulations. Just what's going
through your mind right now and
how proud are you to be picked by the
Saints?
Yes, sir. It just feeling blessed. I'm
just ready to get to work.
Ready to get to work.
What was your contact like with the
Saints before the draft? Did they say
that you visited here? What was What was
that like?
Yes, sir. It just
uh
I can't even describe but it just was a
blessing. I got to work with a lot of
those guys. Coach Joel and a lot of
those guys special teams um in the
Senior Bowl and it's just a blessing,
man. Just to see how, you know, we
connected and interaction. Um just me
bringing the energy and, you know, coach
giving me the opportunity with my, you
know, teammates to let me walk out and
be
um you know, captain during the Senior
Bowl. It just meant a lot to me. I just,
you know, felt like home. Took my, you
know, 40 visit
40 visit down there and, you know, just
a blessing.
Jeremiah, what what do you feel like are
your strengths and what areas you kind
of want to work on right away to get
started?
Yes, sir. So, you know, my strengths,
you know, just being, you know,
a dominant run blocker, being able to
move people and, you know, just be me,
be violent, be a bully. And things I
know I have to work on and, you know,
just pass and run protection and, you
know, just be fixing those little things
like that.
Hey, Jeremiah, can you tell us a little
bit about the the emotions you're
feeling, man? We can see it We can see
it hitting you.
Blessed, man. I just, you know, thank
God, man. Thank God. Thank Just thank
y'all in the organization and everybody
for just taking a chance on the kid from
Selma, man. Just ready to get to work.
Jeremiah, can you talk about your
transition? I guess you started out, you
know, college football defensive tackle
and then what it was like for you
moving to the offensive line.
Yes, sir. It It was a challenge. Um
It was a challenge. It was some ups and
downs
coming in, you know, making the swap
over to D-line and
you know, tearing my ACL and sitting out
a whole year and you know, just making
that transition back over to O-line.
You know, it paid off. Just, you know,
grateful and blessed to be here.
What What made you want to do that and
who was the big influence you on you
make that happen?
Yes, sir. So, I always like in
recruiting process just
I always knew I was going to be the best
offensive lineman. And just, you know,
Armon taking the shot on the on the
Saints to give me a chance
come up there and just do what I do best
and that's be a bully, be able to move
people out of the ball and just come in
and be a game changer, man. Just a
blessing just to
be able to showcase that and also some
things got to clean up but just blessed.
Jeremiah, what did you learn from that
from that experience landing that?
Uh I learned patience. A lot of
patience. A lot of patience. And it's
not going to happen when you want it. Um
going to be a lot of blood, sweat, and
tears. You know, you got guys in front
of you like Derrick Brown, Kobe Wooden.
Um Marcus Harris. Um just being from
guys like Derrick Brown, Marlon Davis
and
guys like that. Just seeing how they
working with they brought to the table.
And for me to just, you know, transition
over and just be like, man,
I see all the hard work and, you know,
talent and everything and
the chemistry that this team has it just
means a lot. So, it's like I know I had
to step my game up coming in as a
freshman and I was ready to play. It
just meant a lot.
How do you feel that
what the Saints do on offense with your
meetings and conversations, things like
that? How do you feel that that plays
into what you what your strengths are
and what you do well?
Can you repeat that? Kind of went out of
here. Um
how does what you've learned about what
the Saints do just through your meetings
and things like that?
How does what it is that they do
fit what you do best?
Yes, sir. So, basically, you know, just
having the meeting with coach, like I
said, coming in on my visit.
Just seeing that having a meeting in
position special position work.
Um just meant a lot trans transition
over from, you know, plays and calls
that we ran in college and similar terms
to, you know, what they have and coach
was like, man,
we pretty much we don't we don't got
much to say since we been y'all pretty
much know what's going on. You know the
calls and, you know, our calls are
pretty much the same. So, looking
forward to you coming here, you know,
stepping up and doing what you got to
do.
So, does this feel kind of like a
perfect fit for you on your side, too,
then? Hell yeah. Yes, sir.
Jeremiah, you
if my numbers are right, 370 pass
blocking assignments and you only had
three penalties. Is that something
that's accurate? Is that something you
concentrated on?
Yes, sir. So, definitely like false
start and penalties didn't have none of
those even though that was like a bigger
issue during the season um for our
offensive line but
um definitely had those
uh those three calls I know two of them
for sure was
I'd say all three definitely on me. Some
of them I could have
I could have did better at but just
blessed and grateful.
Jeremiah, uh
being from Selma, how important You
talked a little bit about it before but
how important was that for you to play
in that Senior Bowl and be the captain?
Uh it was very important. So, I don't
know my screen went out yet. It was very
important um especially like I said,
being the captain and my teammates um
voted on me. Coaches voted on me. Just
go out there especially being from
Alabama and go out there and be a
captain and lead. You know, that's
something that I bring to the table and
bring to the
game and
you know, that's what I'm looking
forward to, you know, bring to the
Saints, baby.
Where are you today, Jeremiah?
Um in Selma, Alabama.
Did you grow up a Saints fan?
Um kind of I really wasn't a fan of
nobody. I just watched whoever had big
O-linemen. I just knew one day it could
be me and here I am today.
Was there a big O-lineman that you kind
of modeled your style after that you
liked?
Uh I always I liked it Trent Williams.
He just to be his size and that big and
athletic and moving and
you know, he [snorts] talk trash and he
back it up and that's, you know, kind of
similar to me. Like you going You going
to get the best out of me. I'm coming
and, you know, I'm learning plays and
everything but I'm definitely, you know,
I love to talk. I love to talk.
Sorry if you were asked this already but
you talked about kind of Trent Williams
and and and the size that you bring to
the game. What do you think that that
um your build maybe brings with you
playing on the interior in particular as
opposed to having the edge?
Yes, sir. So,
for me
I always
you know, since I started playing
football in sixth grade I already knew
like I started playing tight end at
first for like a day then I moved over
to um tackle
and kind of went both ways from there
but um definitely transition over to
just me, you know, just being dominant,
being a bully, being aggressive. Um like
my coach told me in college um coach
Thorn just, you know, control
aggression. That's like a big word for
me and I'm going to keep that with me
you know, for the rest of my life. Just
me being a player just having that
control aggression cuz me I could be the
best there is but when I'm out there and
you know, let my feelings and emotions
get the best of me. You know, that kind
of got to improve on that but definitely
Why only tight end for a day?
Um
I don't know if it was the quarterback
or if I was, you know, my little 5-yard
out or slant or something like that. You
know, definitely kept a drop like
out of three passes I dropped one. But
coach was like, damn, man, you kind of
like I was a big guy. I say about 315,
305.
Yeah.
Anything else for Jeremiah?
All right. Appreciate you taking the
time. Congrats again, man. Yes, sir.
Thank you.